



Saba Katsadze

Nationality: Georgian Date of birth: 12/12/1999 Gender: Male

Carifornia Phone number: (+44) 07519297404

Email address: katsadzesaba2@gmail.com

WhatsApp Messenger: 07519297404

f Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/saba.kacadze.7

Website: https://ss19991212.github.io/Saba_CV.github.io/

• Home: Glasgow, G72 8UR Glasgow (United Kingdom)

ABOUT ME

Driven and tenacious young professional from Georgia. With a bachelor's degree in International Relations. Currently pursuing a Master's degree in Central and East European, Russian and Eurasian studies through the Erasmus Mundus Joint Master's Degree program. I have a diverse range of internship experiences. My professional background includes a role at US Embassy in Tbilisi, at Public Affairs Section, internship in the department of Planning, Research and International Relations at the National Center of Education Quality Enhancement of Georgia and at the Communications Department at the Administration of the President of Georgia. These experiences have provided me with valuable insights into public relations, communications and strategic-planning.

Recently I have started expanding my skillset and have become interested in the promising field of Digital Marketing. I have obtained the certificate from Google's Digital Garage, Digital Marketing course, alongside Coursera's Specialization in SEO course. As well as Codeacademy's certificate of HTML/CSS to complement my SEO skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern of the Public Affairs Secion

United States Embassy in Georgia [30/06/2020 - 22/01/2021]

City: Tbilisi

Country: Georgia

Member of the Press Team. Mainly tasked with preparing daily news reports, translating and preparing transcripts.

Intern of the Planning, Research and International Relations Department

LEPL National Center for Education Quality Enhancement [01/09/2021 – 10/01/2022]

Country: Georgia

Mainly tasked with double-checking, reviewing and translating documents, as well as assisting other members of the team in executing day-to-day tasks.

Intern of the Communications Office

Administration of the President of Georgia [22/12/2021 - 03/2022]

City: Tbilisi

Country: Georgia

Monitoring political trends domestically and abroad. Working on President's visibility through website and social media management. Preparing daily news reports and assisting the staff in administrative duties.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

International Master's in Central and East European, Russian and Eurasian Studies

Tartu, Glasgow & Jagiellonian Universities [08/09/2023 - Current]

City: Glasgow

Country: United Kingdom

Student

Caucasus University [03/10/2018 - 05/2022]

Address: 1 Paata Saakadze Street,

Website: https://cu.edu.ge/

Delegate at European School of Policy and Reforms

Konrad Adenauer Stiftung

Website: https://www.kas.de/de/home

Delegate at Global Challenges Forum 2019

Future Diplomats' Club

Website: https://www.facebook.com/FutureDiplomatsClub/

Certificate of Participation in the Yearly Student Conference - 2021

Caucasus University

Website: https://cu.edu.ge/

Certificate of Participation in the Essay competition of "NATO, Georgia and Current Security Challenges: The 2018 Brussels Summit And Beyond"

Embassy of Bulgaria

Website: https://www.mfa.bg/en/embassies/georgia

Certificate of SEO

Coursera

Country: United Kingdom Website: Coursera.org

Certificate of Google's Digital Marketing Course

Google

Country: United Kingdom **Website:** <u>Google.com</u>

HTML & CSS Certificate

CodeAcademy

Country: United Kingdom Website: Codeacademy.com

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Georgian

Other language(s):

English Russian

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C1 LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1 SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1

French Spanish

LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING A2 LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING A2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2 SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2

Polish

LISTENING AT READING AT WRITING AT

SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 **SPOKEN INTERACTION** A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Basic Digital Marketing / Basic Knowledge of SEO / Copywriting (basic) / HTMI & CSS / Google (Google Ads, Google Analytics) / Microsoft Excel